#### Contact

+905524585490 (Mobile) amir.marjani34@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amirmarjani-6086a6170 (LinkedIn) oceanweb.ir (Personal)

## Top Skills

Angular Material PHP React.js

# amir marjani

Frontend Developer at Fintranet

Istanbul

# Summary

When you enjoy what you do, Work becomes play. I'm Amir Marjani, Programmer and web designer with 5+ years of experience. skilled with about 3 programming language and approximately 10 different framework. Designed and developed over 15 advanced applications from use cases and functional requirements. One of my honors is that I try to learn something new every day.

# Experience

Fintranet
Frontend Developer
September 2021 - Present (4 months)
London, England, United Kingdom

Natum Games Frontend Developer May 2021 - August 2021 (4 months)

Myth Arena is an Turkish e-sports platform where you can support them while watching your favorite broadcasters and improve your skills by participating in competitive events.

Smart Runners Frontend Developer August 2020 - May 2021 (10 months) Tehran, Iran

Project of a sports social media designed in both Persian and English. this project is mainly to publish sports clips recorded by the company's smart cameras.

we used:
angular material in client side
asp.net core in back-end side
and microsoft SQL server
Kits we used:
Angular material

#### bootstrap

Order Bros
Gaming shop
July 2020 - October 2020 (4 months)
Tehran, Iran

A store for a company for trading gaming device.

here we used angular version 9 as client.

php used in this this project as back-end and mySql for database.

universal rendering and preRendering also used in this project.

this project included bootstrap, angular material and AOS library.

Emarat Novin Commercial Company 5 months

Store Manager April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months) Tehran, Iran

A windows application to manage store and ware using Angular Electron as client side
Using pure php as backend and also mySql as Database
Every single part designed by a specific color

Sales and marketing management January 2020 - May 2020 (5 months) Tehran, Iran

In this project we've used Angular framework as front, PHP as backend and MySql as database.

This project include four parts

- Admin management panel
- Operator management panel
- Marketer management panel
- Landing page to introduce product and company

Here we used Ant Design library, google map APIs

This project is made for the purpose of:

Marketers add their customers to database.

Admin manages the reports.

Operators prepare the orders.

Abnie Negar Vazne Introduction and resume of construction company February 2020 - March 2020 (2 months) Iran

Angular 9 has used in this project Php back-end and mySql as database www.vazne-negar.ir

360 Celsius Front End developer June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months) Iran

Network marketing about.

Angular 7,8 Front End.

.Net core Back end.

SQL data base.

IRAN and Emirate Tennis federation Full stack Web Designer September 2018 - June 2019 (10 months)

UI: using angular 7 which contains lazy loading, universal rendering, interceptors

Frelance worker
Freelance Projects
January 2019 - February 2019 (2 months)
Iran

FrontEnd: angular material

BackEnd : Aspi.net
Database : SQL

National Iranian Gas Company Software Programmer June 2018 - December 2018 (7 months)

## RayaDars

Programmer and web Developer
January 2017 - April 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Angular version 2, Node.js, CouchDB 8 months [Iran education system, Design online exam for professors and teachers (team work)]

Angular version 4, Node.js, CouchDB 3 months [Iran education system, Design online exam for professors and teachers (team work)]

C# windows form ( WPF ) 3 months [ Iran education, DVDs autoruns of 10th, 11th and 12th grade (solo) ]

C# windows form ( WPF ) 3 months [RayaDars company professors and teachers board (Similar to windows paint)]

C# web form (asp.net), MVC, Microsoft SQL Server 3 months [Design Imam Khomeini lending web site (solo) ]

Abdi chain store IT and network supervisor February 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 9 months)

### Education

Islamic Azad University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (February 2017 - June 2019)